<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-01-19T09:59:04+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Ruixi “Peter” Li</title><subtitle>Hi, welcome to my page. My name is Ruixi Li, my friends call me Peter or Pete.  Learn more about me by exploring the site.  Hope you could get a good idea of who I am in the end. Thank you! 
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Happy New Year! (New year resolution)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2020/01/16/Happy-New-Year!.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Happy New Year! (New year resolution)" /><published>2020-01-16T16:30:00+08:00</published><updated>2020-01-16T16:30:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2020/01/16/Happy-New-Year!</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2020/01/16/Happy-New-Year!.html">&lt;p&gt;Hi there, to whomever is reading this post. 
Welcome to my site! To find out more about myself, feel freen to explore the about tab as it will be fill with a lot more content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this post I would like to cover a couple of “new year resolutions” I have for the year of 2020. For all of the resolutions I planned on mentioning in this blog post, I am determine to achieve majority of them to debunk my impression of people’s “new year resolutions”. This is my first time blogging and really substantiate my commitments. I am hoping in this way, I could be more motivated and be more aware of myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Learn more about Computers
 I have just graduated college with a bachelor’s degree in Computer Engineering from the Illinois Institute of Technology. One thing I learned in my four years of college is that learning never stops. I’ve been slacking for the past couple of months because of grad school application, family matters, but I am hoping to pick up my thirst for knowledge and momentum of studying once more.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Here are the ways I would do to achieve mhy goals:&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Posting my novicey analysis on academic paper at least monthly&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Attempting various open source projects&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Sharing my booknotes on online lectures and textbooks&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Summarizing my weekly learning experience at my internship position&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;I would be most likely focusing on computer architecture, machine learning, parallel programming, operating systems and image processing&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Acquire new skills, expand the variety of knowledge base 
 I wish to become verstaile in more aspects. Hence, I signed up for driver school and will work my way to my driver’s license finally. And I have also try to spend a minimum of 20mins per day on language learning app and start learning japanese, as I am a big fan of japanese culture.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Be in a better physical shape
 I longing burden of my is my physical condition. I have always been a large dude. Being a large dude has it’s fair share of benefits but I would like to change it for the better of my health in the future. Towards the end of my undergrad, I am starting to realize the importance of maintaining one’s body.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That being said, I would try to not let words and determination go to vain, I will continuously post my journey on this blog, stay tune.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hi there, to whomever is reading this post. Welcome to my site! To find out more about myself, feel freen to explore the about tab as it will be fill with a lot more content.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to Jekyll!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2019/12/12/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Jekyll!" /><published>2019-12-12T09:38:40+08:00</published><updated>2019-12-12T09:38:40+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2019/12/12/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2019/12/12/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll requires blog post files to be named according to the following format:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YEAR-MONTH-DAY-title.MARKUP&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YEAR&lt;/code&gt; is a four-digit number, &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;MONTH&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;DAY&lt;/code&gt; are both two-digit numbers, and &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;MARKUP&lt;/code&gt; is the file extension representing the format used in the file. After that, include the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'Tom'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">You’ll find this post in your _posts directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run jekyll serve, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.</summary></entry></feed>